export const accordionData = [
  {
    question: "What is the WECEHacks Hackathon?",
    answer:
      "WECEHacks is a 24-hour event where UIUC and other undergraduate students come together to learn, build, and share their experience in software and hardware. We are focused on providing a safe space for historically marginalized groups to learn and grow in the tech industry.",
  },
  {
    question: "What if I don't know how to code?",
    answer:
      "WECEHacks is a beginner-friendly event! We will have workshops and mentors to help you get started. We will also have a beginner track for those who are new to coding, and we encourage hackers to form diverse teams that can bring a range of perspectives and skills to the table. Even if you don't have coding experience, you can still contribute to a team by providing creative ideas, user research, or project management skills.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I design at a hackathon?",
    answer:
      "Yes! If you are an aspiring UX Designer, this is a great opportunity for you to work on a project with developers! ",
  },
  {
    question: "What if I don't have a team?",
    answer:
      "You'll have the chance to meet other hackers by joining our Discord server! We'll have a channel for you to find teammates!",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I get to Champaign, IL?",
    answer: "You can check out our hacker guides on getting to Champaign, IL!",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I continue learning and growing after WECEHacks?",
    answer: "Participating in WECEHacks is just the beginning of your learning journey. Keep in touch with the connections you made during the event and continue to learn coding languages such as HTML/CSS. Consider attending or volunteering at future WECEHacks and continue to build your portfolio and network.",
  },
  {
    question: "Interested in hardware?",
    answer: "During the event, there will be workshops dedicated on learning how to install Arduino IDE on your PC, an intro to Raspberry Pi, and even learn how to use a motion sensor device! You can checkout hardware using your student ID.",
  },
  {
    question: "I am male and use he/him pronouns. Can I still participate?",
    answer: "You must identify as a historically underrepresented gender to participate such as women, or those who identify as non binary. However, we do accept mentor applications through our email.",
  },
  {
    question: "What do you mean by 'minority gender'?",
    answer: "By "minority gender", we mean individuals who identify as women, non-binary, genderqueer, gender non-conforming, or any other gender identity that is not traditionally represented in the tech industry.",
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of projects can we work on?",
    answer: "You can work on any project that you believe will have a positive impact on the tech industry and/or underrepresented communities. We encourage you to tackle sponsor prizes, or a prize category to form an idea of what you can build!",
  },
  {
    question:"How many people can be on a team?",
    answer: "You can have up to 4 people on a team!",
  },
  {
    question: "What if I donâ€™t have a team?",
    answer: "You'll have the chance to meet other hackers by joining our Discord server! We'll have a channel for you to find teammates!",
  },
  {
    question:"What are the judging criteria?",
    answer: "Projects will be judged on creativity, impact, and feasibility. We encourage teams to think about the potential impact of their project and how it can be scaled or implemented in the real world.",
  },
  {
    question:"Will food and drinks be provided?",
    answer:"Yes, we will provide food and drinks throughout the hackathon. If you have any dietary restrictions or preferences, please let us know in advance so that we can accommodate your needs.",
  },
];
